<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
	<string name="app_name">AKA</string>
	
	<string name="mode_label">Hell mode</string>	    
	<string name="help_label">Help</string>
	<string name="exit_label">Exit</string>		
	<string name="settings_label">Settings...</string>
	
	<string name="messageOptions">Message Options</string>    
	
	<string name="help_title">AKA Help</string>    
	<string name="help_text">
	    <b>What is it?</b>
	    \n\nThe Androidomatic Keyer (also known as the AKA) is a memory keyer that 
	    enables you to send either morse code or Hellscreiber mode messages from your 
	    android phone through a radio transmitter. 
	    In contrast to other digital modes, neither requires that the 
	    radio transmit a modulated signal. Both modes switch the radio carrier
	    on and off in a specific pattern. Consequently, they require little
	    bandwidth and perform well even at low power and under noisy conditions.  
	    This means that your radio can be a
	    relatively simple CW transmitter -- perhaps something that
	    you can build yourself. The phone\'s audio
	    output needs to be connected to the radio\'s key jack through a simple interface 
	    consisting of just a few easily obtainable components. Plans for building 
	    such an interface can be found on the Internet at:
	     goo.gl/dummyURLfornow.html.
	     \n\n<b>Operation</b>
	     \n\nThe keyer will send any message 
	    that appears in the message window at the top
	    of the screen. You can either type in a message or select one of the stored 
	    messages. To store a new message, press the "+" key next to the message window. 
	    Once you add a message, the keyer will remember it for next time.
	    If you want to get rid of a stored message, select it for more than a second
	    and then select <b>Delete</b> from the menu that appears. Similarly, if you want 
	    to edit a previous message or copy it to a new message slot, select the message
	    for more than a second and choose either <b>Edit</b> or <b>Copy</b>.
	    \n\nA number of options are available through the menu, including the 
	    ability to switch back and forth between morse code and Hellscreiber modes and to 
	    change settings.\n\n
	    <b>Modes</b>
	    \n\n<u>Morse Code</u>:
	    About morse and relevant.
	    \n\n<u>Hellscreiber</u>: 
	    About Hellscreiber and settings.\n</string>
	   
    <string-array name="messages_array">
        <item>CQ CQ CQ DE AI4SV AI4SV K</item>
        <item>TNX FER CALL UR 599 OP JACK QTH FAIRFAX, VA</item>
        <item>RIG KNWD 450S ANT G5RV 45 FT PWR 5W</item>
        <item>TNX FB QSO ES 73</item>
    </string-array>
    
	<string-array name="message_options_array">
        <item>Edit</item>
        <item>Copy</item>
        <item>Move Up</item>
        <item>Move Down</item>
        <item>Delete</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>