<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    
    <!--  Main Activity -->
	<string name="app_name">AKA</string>
	<string name="instruction_text">Enter message</string>
	<string name="no_messages">No messages have been saved. To save a
         			   new message to a memory slot, enter it 
         			   above and then hit the save button. </string>
         			   
	<string-array name="messages_array">
        <item>CQ CQ CQ DE AI4SV AI4SV K</item>
        <item>TNX FER CALL = UR 599 OP JACK QTH FAIRFAX, VA +</item>
        <item>RIG KNWD 450S ANT G5RV 45 FT PWR 5W</item>
        <item>TNX FB QSO ES 73</item>
	</string-array>
    
	<string-array name="message_options_array">
        <item>Edit</item>
        <item>Copy</item>
        <item>Move Up</item>
        <item>Move Down</item>
        <item>Delete</item>
    </string-array>   
    
	<string name="nothing_to_play">Nothing to play. Enter a message first.</string>
	<string name="enter_message_first">Enter a message first, then save.</string>	    
         			   
	<!-- Main Activity Menu -->    
	
	<string name="toCW_label">CW mode</string>	  
	<string name="toHell_label">HELL mode</string>  
	<string name="help_label">Help</string>	
	<string name="settings_label">Settings...</string>
	<string name="cancel_beacon_label">Beacon</string>
	<string name="enable_beacon_label">Beacon On</string>
	<string name="sk_label">Straight Key</string>
	
	<!-- Main Activity ContextMenu -->
	
	<string name="messageOptions">Message Options</string>   
	<string name="cant_move_up">Can\'t move up any further.</string>
	<string name="cant_move_down">Can\'t move down any further.</string>
	
	<!-- Edit Message Dialog -->
	
	<string name="edit_message_dialog_title">Edit Message</string>
	<string name="edit_message_dialog_ok">OK</string>	    
	<string name="edit_message_dialog_cancel">Cancel</string>
		    
	<!--  Preferences -->    
         			   
    <string name="general_category">General</string>  
    
    <string name="callsign_title">Your Callsign</string>
    <string name="callsign_dialg_title">Callsign</string>
    <string name="callsign_dialog_message">Enter your callsign</string>
    <string name="callsign_default_value">URCALL</string>
    <string name="callsign_summary">Callsign to substitute for @ in the text</string>
 
	<string name="suppress_title">Suppress phone sounds</string>
	<string name="suppress_summary">Suppress all other phone sounds 
	    including ringing and alarms</string>
	
	<string name="cw_category">CW (morse code) mode</string>   
	
    <string name="sidetone_title">Sidetone pitch</string>
    <string name="sidetone_summary">Adjust audible tone</string>
    <string name="wpm_title">Code speed</string>
    <string name="wpm_summary">Adjust speed of sent code</string>
    
	<string name="hell_category">Hellscreiber Mode</string>
	
	<string name="darkness_title">Character darkness</string>
	<string name="darkness_summary">Adjust fine timing</string>
	
	<string name="beacon_category">CW Beacon mode</string> 
	
	<string name="beacon_title">Beacon text</string>   
	<string name="beacon_summary">Message to be sent by beacon</string>
	<string name="beacon_dialog_title">Beacon message</string>
	<string name="beacon_dialog_message">Enter a message</string>
	<string name="beacon_default_value">QTH # DE @/B @/B</string>   
    <string name="beacon_interval_title">Beacon interval</string> 
    <string name="beacon_interval_summary">Define how often beacon is sent</string>
    <string name="qrss_box_title">Enable QRSS beacon</string> 
    <string name="qrss_box_summary">Sends extremely slow morse code</string>  
    <string name="qrss_rate_title">Dit duration</string>
    <string name="qrss_rate_summary">Choose duration of a dit</string>
         			   
    <string name="minutes_3">Every 3 minutes</string>     			   
	<string name="minutes_5">Every 5 minutes</string> 
	<string name="minutes_15">Every 15 minutes</string> 
	<string name="minutes_30">Every 30 minutes</string> 
	<string name="hours_1">Every hour</string> 
	<string name="hours_2">Every 2 hours</string> 
	<string name="hours_6">Every 6 hours</string> 
	
	<string name="seconds_3">3 seconds</string>
	<string name="seconds_5">5 seconds</string>
	<string name="seconds_10">10 seconds</string>
	<string name="seconds_30">30 seconds</string>
	                        

	

	
	<!-- Help -->   
	
	<string name="help_title">AKA Help</string>    
	<string name="help_text"><b>What is it?</b>
	    \n\nThe Androidomatic Keyer (also known as the AKA) is a memory keyer that 
	    enables you to send either morse code or Hellscreiber mode messages from your 
	    android device through a radio transmitter. 
	    In contrast to other digital modes, neither requires that the 
	    radio transmit a modulated signal. Both modes switch the radio carrier
	    on and off in a specific pattern. Consequently, they require little
	    bandwidth and perform well even at low power and under noisy conditions.  
	    This means that your radio can be a
	    relatively simple CW transmitter -- perhaps something that
	    you can build yourself. The android devices\'s audio
	    output needs to be connected to the radio\'s key jack through a simple interface 
	    consisting of just a few easily obtainable components. Plans for building 
	    such an interface can be found on the Internet at:
	     goo.gl/QIgVw.
	    \n\n<b>Operation</b>
	    \n\nThe keyer will send any message 
	    that appears in the message window at the top
	    of the screen. You can either type in a message or select one of the stored 
	    messages. To store a new message, press the "+" key next to the message window. 
	    Once you add a message, the keyer will remember it for next time.
	    If you want to get rid of a stored message, select it for more than a second
	    and then select <b>Delete</b> from the menu that appears. Similarly, if you want 
	    to edit a previous message or copy it to a new message slot, select the message
	    for more than a second and choose either <b>Edit</b> or <b>Copy</b>.
	    \n\nA number of options are available above the edit window. Selecting Hell/CW will
	    toggle between these two modes. Any message already being played will complete in 
	    whatever mode it originated. Selecting Beacon will start a count down to sending the
	    cw beacon message, and selecting the countdown will turn the beacon off. If a beacon
	    is playing, selecting the countdown will not interrupt the current message. Other 
	    beacon settings are found under the setting menu. Finally, between the mode and beacon
	    text at the top of the screen, there is a cartoon alien. Clicking the alien will put
	    the device into straight key mode. In that mode, tapping the alien will key the 
	    transmitter. To return to the main screen, use the device\'s back button.
	    \n\n<b>Settings</b>
	    \n\nPressing the menu button will bring up options including a settings menu. After
	    selecting the settings menu, a new screen will appear with controls for various 
	    setting affecting the general behavior of the application, as well as specific items 
	    pertaining to CW, Hellscreiber, and beacon modes. To leave the settings menu, use the
	    device\'s back button. Settings should persist between sessions.
	    \n\n<b>Modes</b>
	    \n\n<u>Morse Code</u>: Morse
	    code has been around in various forms since the mid-19th Century, and its staying power
	    reflects several key advantages over other communication modes.
	    Anything that transmits an on/off
	    signal can send morse code, be it a flashlight or radio transmitter. Decoding morse code
	    does not need fancy computational equipment -- just some training. Morse code signals
	    occupy a tiny portion of bandwidth and can be distinguished from noise even under 
	    conditions where many other signaling modes would fail.
	    \n\nIn addition to the standard international morse code, the keyer supports the extended 
	    Latin character set, for example for characters like é, ç and ø. Additionally, the
	    keyer supports Russian morse and Japanese wabun code variants, when messages are entered
	    in Cyrillic and Katakana characters, respectively. Not every extended punctuation character 
	    is implemented, as these are very uncommon in morse code messages.
	    \n\nSpecial Symbols: As a convenience, you can abbreviate some common items with a single
	    character.
	    \n\n<b>@</b>  Your Callsign (from Settings)\n
	    <b>#</b>  GPS Coordinates\n 
	    <b>!</b>  Maidenhead Grid Location\n
	    <b>=</b>  prosign BT\n
	    <b>+</b>  prosign AR\n
	    <b>~</b>  prosign KN\n
	    <b>*</b>  prosign SK\n\n
	    <b>)</b>  prosign DO (begin wabun encoding)\n
	    <b>(</b>  prosign SN (end wabun encodoing)\n
	    
	    \n\n<u>Hellscreiber</u>: 
	    \n\nHellscreiber is also an on/off mode, which sends a graphic representation of characters. It
	    was invented in the early 20th Century. Originally, it was received and printed on strips of 
	    paper, but today any PC with a sound input can decode this mode. Because it is graphic, messages
	    benefit from the human visual system\'s ability to pick symbols out of noise. Consequently, it is 
	    also very immune to noise and suitable for low power transmission. The bandwidth of a Hellscreiber
	    signal is about 300 Hz, so wider than CW, but it is still considered a narrow bandwidth mode.
	    \n\nOperation in Hell mode is similar to CW mode, except the character set is more limited: the original
	    Hellscreiber font was limited to 
	    the Latin alphabet, numbers, and a few punctuation symbols. 
	    This keyer includes some extended Latin characters, the Russian alphabet, and additional punctuation
	    symbols. The Hellscreiber font is a 7x7 matrix, which
	    makes it difficult to represent more complicated glyphs. Any 
	    non-printing characters will be replaced by a space. Note that the spaces have a small tick mark, 
	    which is a hold over from when it was desirable to keep a vox activated for the duration of a message.
	    \n\nHellscreiber is sent at 2.5 characters per second, or 122.5 baud. Some radios disregard keydowns 
	    of less than about 5 milliseconds, but the smallest transmitted element of Hellscreiber 
	    has a send duration of 8.163 milliseconds, which should be long enough to key most rigs. To prevent 
	    keyclicks and consequent widening of the signal, radios shape the carrier envelope when keyed on and off.
	    Instead of transmitting a square wave, the carrier amplitude ramps up and down, giving the attack and
	    decay a more rounded appearance and minimizing bandwidth. As a consequence, full carrier only occurs
	    for a portion of the key down period, and Hell characters may appear thinner and lighter when received. To
	    compensate, there is a darkness control under the <i>Settings</i> menu, which can increase the duration of 
	    dark elements. The same setting can be used to lighten a character, but care should be taken to avoid 
	    excessive shortening, which would increase the required bandwidth.
	    \n\n<u>Beacon Mode</u>
	    \n\nThe keyer can be set up to send short morse code messages at regular intervals. The message and 
	    repetition rate are set under the Settings menu, and the beacon is activated through the main menu. The 
	    beacon can be set to send QRSS morse code, where a single dit can take several seconds to send. This is 
	    a weak signal mode, but be sure that your transmitter can handle the long key down periods.
	    </string>
	

</resources>